urm.academy 2017-06-15

# Privacy Policy - Unstoppable Recording Machine

(1) Introduction

This privacy policy sets out how Unstoppable Recording Machine LLC uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this web site and our products/services. We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

(2) Information We Collect

If you choose to use this web site and our products/services, we may require you to provide contact and identity information including:

Your name, address, email address, and other basic contact information.  
Communications and other messages, including correspondence betweenUnstoppable Recording Machine LLC and you.  
Non-personally identifiable information that we gather, including your IP address, computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from this web site and individual pages on this web site and data that we may collect through cookies or other means.  
General information regarding our products/services you have registered to receive.

Unstoppable Recording Machine LLC uses Google Analytics and Google Analytics User-ID to gather additional information and we abide by Google’s terms as such that we do not share any of this data with anyone for any reason.

We have implemented Google Analytics Advertising Features such as Demographics and Interest reporting, Re-marketing, GDN Impression Reporting, and the Double Click Campaign Manager integration. This means we have enabled Google Analytics to collect data about our traffic via Google Advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers, in addition to the data collected through a standard Google Analytics implementation. We will never facilitate the merging of personally-identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information collected through any Google advertising product or feature without your consent to that merger.

(3) Our Use and Disclosure of Your Information

We may use your Personal Information to:

Provide our products/services.  
Resolve disputes, calculate and collect fees, and troubleshoot problems.  
Verify your identity and the information you provide.  
Encourage a safe online experience and enforce our terms and conditions.  
Improve our products/services and customer experience and inform you about our products/services and updates.  
Provide you with information that may affect your use of our products/services.  
Communicate marketing and promotional offers to you.  
We do not sell or rent your Personal Information to third parties. We may share, and you hereby consent to our sharing of, personal information with the following:

Service providers and affiliates who assist in the delivery of our products/services we provide to you, the enforcement of our terms and conditions, and the promotion of trust and safety.  
Third parties if we believe that disclosure is advisable or necessary to comply with the law, to enforce or apply our terms and conditions, or to protect the rights, property or safety of Unstoppable Recording Machine LLC or others. This may include exchanging information with other companies and organisations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

We will not share any Google User-ID information with anyone, ever. For more information on opt-ing out of these features, visit https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/

(4) External Links

This website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
